作词 : cAnON.
作曲 : Hiroyuki Sawano
Because you seem feeling down
因为你看起来感觉失落
I've been trying to calm & fade it
我试着让你静下来 淡忘往事
But you don't wanna turn around
但你并不想有所转变
Teenage is so complicated
年轻人的心中所想总是如此复杂
Cmon, cmon
加油 来吧
Ain't no one who can take your place
一定会有人能读懂你的心
Oh baby...please let me see you smiling
让我看到你的笑容
It's such a pain in the neck we have homework by tomorrow
明天就要交家庭作业是何其令人生厌的事情
I know you're not a person who would be worn out with sorrow
我知晓你并不是一个只知悲伤的人
告别过去真是不容易 还带着些许的迷惘
To fly away from your past is not so easy but dizzy
Keep your faith
坚守你的初衷与信念
Raise your lively face
仰起你年轻果敢的脸
Just get rid of your broken wings
忘记曾经破碎的翅膀
You're strong enough by now
如今你已足够强大
I'll be your spark when you're lost in the dark
当你迷失在黑暗中 让我做你的启明之光
And let me be your sun, be your match to
让我作为你的太阳 为你指引前进的方向
Light your heart up
点亮你的心灵
If you want to
如果你愿意如此
Light your heart up
点亮你的心灵
Besides you lead a winding road
你身旁是条蜿蜒扭曲的路
There're some troubles make you stumble
一路上会遇到如此多的困难阻碍你前行
But you're gonna beat them all
但你一定要战胜他们
Loner girl is hard to crumble
孤独少女 却很少崩溃
I know, I know
我知道 我知道
Ain't no one who can touch your heart
一定会有人能读懂你的心
But baby...please let me see you crying
让我看到你的笑容
You're sort of square
你是多么老实呀
Why don't we ditch that class?
为什么我们不选择翘课呢
It's time to chill out
是时候冷静下来
I know you're not a person who would get excited and shout
我知晓你不是一个激动的女孩
The sky above your thick cloud is not so gritty but pretty
叆叇的天空上面 并不是那么坚强却漂亮
Keep your faith
坚守你的初衷与信念
Raise your lively face
仰起你年轻果敢的脸
Just get rid of your broken wings
忘记曾经破碎的翅膀
You're strong enough by now
如今你已足够强大
I'll be your spark when you're lost in the dark
当你迷失在黑暗中 让我做你的启明之光
And let me be your sun, be your match to
让我作为你的太阳 为你指引前进的方向
点亮你的心灵
Light your heart up
Keep your faith
坚守你的初衷与信念
Raise your lively face
仰起你年轻果敢的脸
Just get rid of your broken wings
忘记曾经破碎的翅膀
You're strong enough by now
如今你已足够强大
I'll be your spark when you're lost in the dark
当你迷失在黑暗中 让我做你的启明之光
And let me be your sun, be your match to
让我作为你的太阳 为你指引前进的方向
Light your heart up
点亮你的心灵
If you want to
如你愿意
点亮你的心灵
Light your heart up
Sing it now, sing it loud
那么现在，大声唱出你心中所想
Sha la la...
sha la la la la la la ~
I'm your buddy all the way
我会一直做你的挚友
You may thank me day by day
一复一日你也许会感激我为你所做